ELEUSIS
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [ATU XIIII – ס – PATH 25 – ♐ – ⚄⚀] ☋

eleusis
they carry on the war
to keep us
from discovering the source
inside our bones
the memory is old
so dig deep
and watch its wings unfold

once through the hole, tunneling deep into the heart of the earth, the lines between the interior and the exterior are dissassembled, dissolved, undone, cast into a sea of light and subject to informational assimilation into the unified center of things. all opposition is annihilated in the waking of the suntide.

press on

eleusis
i see you in my dreams
or somewhere
that feels like in between
the cracks in our heads
that let in all the light
are growing
let's rip them open wide

true sight requires dedicated practice and a firm resolve to remain compassionate with the inner child through times of great distress and turmoil. the dark night of the soul must be confronted with courage and passed through by way of total surrender to the dawning light of the higher star. 

press on

eleusis
shining like the sun
the way home
is revealed in the dawn
magnum opus
the seals are released
so wake up
to the κυκεών redeemed

awareness suffuses all that is with the subtle glow of indra's reflections, beads of dew transmitting thought across endless gaps at the speed of the instant now. unbind the body! free the emotions! unshackle the mind! what is true always rises to the surface of a deep well of stillness.

⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
♐ 
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕