EYE OF GIZA
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [ATU XIII – נ – PATH 24 – ♏ – ⚃⚅] ☋

eye of giza, eye of sight
i beseech thee, grant me flight
thunder roaring across the plains
eye of giza teach me my name

the pyramids at giza, timeless wonders of the world, consciousness-focusing crystals, gateways of interdimensional star-travel. the crackle that rends the veil along the column of the middle wand of sushumna heralds an awakening electrical storm. sacred names must be adopted for sacred times.

dark companion come to life
in the womb of paradise
icy waters and stormy gales
now transmuted into sunlight

creature of the subconscious, lovecraftian faces of the deep! all is well that finds its roots in the heart of the earth, deep within the inner light of being that radiates forth nerve-like connections to each and every one of the children of ra, descendents of horus, protectorate of sekhmet. the sun and moon must be wedded, and the conjuct passed through the process of death to embrace regeneration in the now.

eye of giza

step up to the lofty peak
rarified and out of reach
i see out and become the whole
empyrean wheels turning

the mountaintop is clear, generating its own heavenly climate due to its physical structure, its stony bones a painted echo of the spiritual form of the landscape. from a great height, a new perspective may be established. angels visit with those with open hearts who reside on the peaks.

eye of giza

⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
♏
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕