MERGE
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [ATU II – ג – PATH 13 –☽ – ⚂⚀] ☋

impossible thing
you are a part of me
improbable dream
you hold the moonlit key
abandon the scales
embrace the synthesis
surrender your tales
you can be limitless

focus in the higher planes must be built, but it also operates as a gift bestowed piece by piece. test those who would guide. seek out love with the pure whiteness of fresh snow, and then give the egoic self over completely in the total trust that true lovers share.

so i merge with an ocean of light

arational being
hidden just underneath
peel back off the screens
fractal eternity
vibrational forms
cascading rainbow rays
the veil is torn
become the dawning day

mesmerizing depth of detail – the oceans of the akashic layers require a steadiness of mind that arises like a lotus from the still mud of the properly prepared earthen body of clay. passing further still, angelic prisms of form repeat and refract until the inner light emerges, opening briatic planes that unfold with jaw-rending sighs of purring release.

so i merge with an ocean of light


⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
☽ 
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕