THE STAR
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [ATU XVII – ה – PATH 28 – ♒ – ⚄⚃] ☋

a star
anchored in choronzon sky
who am i to touch you
who am i to speak your name
a star
echoing a six-rayed sun
deep inside it's shining
rosy cross reveal your source

the seven-rayed bolt from above casts a fishhook through the abyss, carving out a sure path of return for the one who is able to witness the five-petaled rose being birthed from the four-armed cross of death. the holy one floats in the in-between, hovering as the eye in the midst of fire and water intertwined to construct the hex of earth.

all around me now
fall upon me now

the star
bridge to mercy's monolith
רזיאל‎ in glory
vision of a lofty glyph
the star
veiled in the loving hex
lay to rest your sorrow
underneath the lake of fire

the breath is the heart's true path to wisdom, the crystal key that vibrates with the strength of ages. though the path is reliable, tests lie in the act of opening. in order for the places that cry out for healing to be heard and brought out into the light of the cosmic wind, in order for vitality to arise from the sacral depths, in order for the electric serpent to once again ascend to her thousand-petaled height and don her crown as the ancient of days, the abyss must be embraced, its depths plumbed through joyful, breathless swimming. mysteries are revealed in the eternal white wisdom of the tail of the celestial yod.

all around me now
fall upon me now

⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
♒
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕