THE HIEROPHANT
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [ATU V – ו  – PATH 16 – ♉ – ⚂⚃] ☋

the hierophant
merciful window
through the great abyss
to the other side
hierophant
you are a portal
ancient mask of light
unfurl the ladder to the stars

all truths are lies, all religions of the book falsehoods, all faces masks. stories designed to instruct must be eventually rescinded in submission to the higher light of wisdom cast upon areas of success and completion. in this way, the garden of the initiate's interior is cultivated until the day of harvest, when wisdom greets the merciful ascension face to face.

kneel
feel
heal

purple beyond every purple
in celestial path
third eye open wide
vishuddhi
abandon your tension
leave it all behind
spread your wings now
take to flight

the door to the inner realms may appear obscure due to blockages in the body, resistances lodged in the etheric fabric that coat the experience with the colored veil of apparent reality. the higher chakras opened and energized, a great work of healing begins, at first in the body of the initiate, and then spreading outwards with the tender ferocity of a star being born to shine in newness of light.

kneel
feel
heal

⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
♉
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕