THE KINGDOM
⧊⧫⟠✡⟠◊⧊
⧉
◊✡⧫

☊ [EMANATION X – מלכות‎ – PATH 10 – ⊕ – ⚁⚃] ☋

do you stop to think
of who you are
and where you're headed
are you on the brink
do you see the cracks
can you read the writing on the wall

there is always a river running underneath. the fountain of the interior is ever alive with new energy, though it may be buried and discarded for years, for lifetimes. awareness dawns in stages, but builds with a cumulative acceleration, approaching singularity soon after the depth work begins in earnest.

but you will get there

why don't you wake up wake up wake up
when you wake up you will wake up in my arms
we will wake up wake up wake up 
when i wake up i will wake up as a star

show me how to understand the delicate nature of this divine plan
open my eye to the one eternally luminous fractal sun
inhale love with every breath and breathe out smoke so full of it
see the world around you set free

there is a world behind this one, a reality that our sense-field displays are built upon as skins over an astral framework, informed to its very core by the code that lies beneath. all is flux; the hyle of assiah flows across the gridded expanse of time as a river. everything is made of light. every thing is made of light. see the glow around the edges of things? the process is manifest at this present moment.

yeah you will get there
we will get there

why don't you wake up wake up wake up
when you wake up you will wake up in my arms
we will wake up wake up wake up 
when we wake up we will wake up as a star

⚚ ⌬ ☤ ⚛ ⚕ 
⊕
⊗⧉⊙⧉⊕